(Sheldon:)Your heart might be
in the right place,
(Sheldon:)but your head, chest
and arms certainly aren't.
Anyway, the funeral's on Sunday.
(Sheldon:)But, that's Star Wars Day.
(Leonard:)Yeah...
(Leonard:)Of all the things about this
that are sad,
(Leonard:)that might not be number one.
You OK?
I know he meant a lot to you.
(Sheldon:)I'm fine.
(Howard:)OK.
(Leonard:)Yet he cried when they changed
the Raisin Bran box.
(Professor Proton(on youtube):)This is something
interesting, boys and girls.
(Professor Proton(on youtube):)After an owl eats,
he spits up part of his meal,
that he cant digest,
in the form of a pellet.
(Professor Proton(on youtube):)Is.... isn't that a hoot?
(Professor Proton(on youtube):)We'll be right back
after I fire my writers.